bestgamewallpapers.com 2018-05-16

# Privacy Policy

BestGameWallpapers.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## Logged information

No personal information is collected about the visitors.

BestGameWallpapers.com logs only statistical information about browsers, operating systems, and referring websites for security and statistical purposes. None of this information is distributed to any third party.

## Email Addresses

If you contact us via email for any reason, your email address will be kept private and will not be passed on to any third party.

## Cookies

The owners/managers of BestGameWallpapers.com do not set any cookies to visitors computer, although, in the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a cookie on your computer.

## Third-Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. BestGameWallpapers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of these web sites.

## Acceptance of this Policy

By visiting BestGameWallpapers.com, you signify your assent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

Platforms: PC, PS2, PS3, PSP, Xbox, X360, Wii, DS, GameCube, GBA.   
WQHD (2560x1440) and Full HD (1920x1080) resolution quality. 

[Submit wallpapers](mailto:alex@bestgamewallpapers.com) | Sitemap | Privacy
